{
    "subject": "resource/Wagon_Master",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "Wagon Master is a Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9542489647865295,
            "question": "Is Wagon Master a real film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9428091049194336,
            "question": "Is Wagon Master considered a classic film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9149049520492554,
            "question": "Who directed Wagon Master?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8723169565200806,
            "question": "What are some similar films to Wagon Master?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.704694926738739,
            "question": "What genre is Wagon Master?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6246238350868225,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in Wagon Master?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6102477312088013,
            "question": "What type of work is Wagon Master?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5746515989303589,
            "question": "Where can I watch Wagon Master?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5556397438049316,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of Wagon Master?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43678364157676697,
            "question": "What year was Wagon Master released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Wagon Master is a Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8722_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of Wagon Master?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8722_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch Wagon Master?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8722_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work is Wagon Master?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8722_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8722_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8722_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8722_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8722_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8722_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8722_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8722_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8722_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8722_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8722_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that, according to the context information provided, there are multiple documents that describe \"Wagon Master\" as a film, such as \"Wagon Master is a classic Western film...\" and \"Wagon Master is an American western from 1950 film directed by John Ford.\" Therefore, the statement \"Wagon Master is a Film\" is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references that confirm \"Wagon Master\" is indeed a film, directed by John Ford and released in 1950."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}